[Music]
Hello Hello,
how to become an agent, what are the benefits of becoming one,
how can one become one and what is its simple and
easy process, I will
try to give you complete information about it in this video, I
request all of you, those who are
visiting the channel for the first time, please subscribe to the channel,
comment and definitely share so that
more and more people can benefit from this channel, so let's
quickly see
what is the process of becoming an agent of ICICI Lombard, I will tell you the benefits of becoming it,
then I will come to its process,
if I talk about the health segment
because three things are done very well here, for those who will
become an agent of ICC Lombard, health insurance
is a preferable topic and there is content for which one should work, the
best work of health insurance is done in ICC Lombard, in this
you will also get very
good and good payouts, secondly
here you can do motor insurance
and non-motor insurance, but
our focus remains solely on health insurance,
so I request all of you who
want to become an agent of Lombard and
genuinely from 15%  If you want a great payout of up to 35%, not only that, but also a
renewal payment and a renewal commission of
15% for life. If you want to earn it, then do
n't miss this opportunity and
join as soon as possible. Joining here is
very simple and without any exam. A great
opportunity has come, friends.
For all those people who want to work in this insurance industry for the first time, the
full
code is available. Their court opens within two days.
This is available for those
friends who do not already have any
help from any broker, only those
people can get ICC Lombard passport. There is no
fee,
no exam, your code will be generated within two days. In
which you can do all the work related to health,
motorcycle and
assembly work simultaneously. But I would
like to explain it to you again in detail. Our entire focus is on health insurance,
so if you join keeping health in mind, you will
get more benefits. Not only this,
here you
can do all kinds of work, part time, full time. People who are
employed somewhere or in any business,  Those who want to
grow it can also do it
and those who want to make a full time career in insurance business
can also join it and the best
part is friends, it is on a fully digital
platform, for this there will be
no need to go to any branch, you
just have to contact me, this is my
WhatsApp number, write your passport number on it,
I will share the complete details with you,
after sharing your code will be created within two days
and you can start working comfortably, if
you are already an agent of any company
then you will have to send the documents of any family member
whose name does
not have any code, this is very clear, there should
not be confusion for this again and again, if you want to do
something big in life, achieve something big
and make your career in the insurance segment, then
you will not get a better opportunity than this anywhere else, I
hope you will understand the concept working,
Namaskar
[Sangeet]